has a stop that calls perceived value
the same product
different packaging
can be worth much more
and today twenty-four
I will show you what this really is
I mean
it costs 10reais
it costs 15reais
now it costs 20reais
I'm going to go into the galleries and try to generate value
not with this here
but like this
sorry
all right
sorry bother you
you who own here
your name is
I fall with pleasure
I ordered a coffee now
I'm not one to complain no
but in fact it is
it's wonderful
congratulations
leave your from the Passenger workshop for you
use a toolbox to
fix people's day
and here is 20g of happiness
and wanted to leave it as a courtesy
for you to know our products
case you are interested
there's my contact who's the Passenger's workshop
no Instagram
our very authentic mass
thank you
hope you like your time
it's good it's good
thanks saw man
I think it will be good bro
ah Cara
if this Dar good will be my 1st old trading point
just keep talking to me AI Caio
love strawberry
then I will give my version of love strawberry
What
haha